// example of final product
Map<String, dynamic> database = {
  'folders': {
    1: {
      'folderName': 'Java',
      'insideFolder': {
        'folders': {
          1: {
            'folderName': 'arrays',
            'questions': {
              1: {
                'question': 'what is array',
                'answer': 'collection of data',
              },
              2: {
                'question': 'what is index',
                'answer': 'address of array',
              },
            },
          },
          'questions': {
            1: {
              'question': 'what is java',
              'answer': 'a programming language',
            },
            2: {
              'question': 'java strengths',
              'answer': 'robust, fast, and multi platform',
            },
          },
        },
      }
    },
    2: {
      'folderName': 'Javascript',
      'insideFolder': {
        'folders': {
          1: {
            'folderName': 'HTML',
            'questions': {
              1: {
                'question': 'what is HTMK',
                'answer': 'a hypertext markup language',
              },
            },
          },
          2: {
            'folderName': 'CSS',
            'questions': {
              1: {
                'question': 'what is css',
                'answer': 'a cascading style sheet',
              },
            },
          },
        },
        'questions': {
          1: {
            'question': 'what is javascript',
            'answer': 'a programming language for web',
          },
          2: {
            'question': 'javascript weakness',
            'answer': 'messy',
          },
        },
      },
    },
    3: {
      'folderName': 'Augy chan',
      'insideFolder': {
        'folders': {},
        'questions': {
          1: {
            'question': 'what is august',
            'answer': 'he is love',
          },
          2: {
            'question': 'what is love',
            'answer': 'august period.',
          },
        },
      },
    },
  },
};
